Who do you believe?
Capturing the Friedmans is a documentary, crime film directed by Andrew Jarecki.
An Oscar nominated documentary about a middle-class American family who is torn apart when the
father Arnold and son Jesse are accused of sexually abusing numerous children.
Director Jarecki interviews people from different sides of this tragic story and raises the question of whether they
were rightfully tried when they claim they were innocent and there was never any evidence against them.
Self (archive footage), played by Arnold Friedman.
Self, played by Elaine Friedman.
Self, played by David Friedman.
Self, played by Jesse Friedman.
Self (archive footage), played by Seth Friedman.
Self - Postal Inspector, played by John McDermott.
Capturing the Friedmans is a 2003 HBO documentary
film directed by Andrew Jarecki.
It focuses on the 1980s investigation of Arnold and
Jesse Friedman for child molestation.
The film premiered at the 2003 Sundance Film Festival where it received
critical acclaim as well as the Grand Jury Prize: Documentary.
The film went on to be nominated for the Academy
Award for Best Documentary Feature.
The film explores themes of pedophilia, sexual abuse,
child pornography, sodomy, middle class.